Register of the Don Mulford Papers, 1963-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
Don Mulford Papers
1963-1971
83032
Hoover Institution Archives
4 manuscript boxes (1.7 linear feet)
Correspondence, reports, bulletins, clippings, and government documents, relating to subversive activities and radicalism in California, and especially to student radicalism, primarily at the University of California, Berkeley.
Mulford, Don, 1915-
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1983.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
1915, August 27 Born, Oakland, California
1939 AB, University of California, Berkeley
1957 Elected to California State Assembly, 18th District
1957-present California state legislator
1982-present State Chief of Protocol for Northern California
Scope and Contents note
Correspondence, reports, bulletins, clippings, and government documents, relating to subversive activities and radicalism in California, and especially to student radicalism, primarily at the University of California, Berkeley.
University of California, Berkeley.; California.; Radicalism--United States.; Student movements--United States.; Subversive activities--United States.; United States--Politics and government.; Universities and colleges--United States.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1963-1971 (Box 1-4)
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence, reports, bulletins, clippings, government documents pertaining to radicalism and left-wing movements in the United States, primarily in the Bay Area in California.
  - Academic freedom (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aquinas Foundation (Folder 2)
  - Anti-draft movements (Folder 3)
  - Anti-ROTC movements (Folder 4)
  - Berkeley (Folder 5-6)
  - Black activism and Black Panthers (Folder 7-8)
  - Campus revolutionaries (Folder 9)
  - Campus unrest (Folder 10-11)
  - Davis, Angela (Folder 12)
  - Drugs (Folder 13)
  - Oakland Boycott, 1968 (Folder 14)
  - Peace groups (Folder 15)
  - Peoples Park, Berkeley, 1969
    - General (Folder 16)
    - General (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Military Department report (Folder 2)
  - Radicalism in the United States (Folder 3-7)
  - Radicalism in the United States (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - State Senate Factfinding Subcommittee on Un-American Activities, Analysis of the Thirteenth Report of the, 1965 (Folder 2A)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) (Folder 3)
  - Terrorism (Folder 3A)
  - University of California
    - Berkeley
      - General, 1966-68 (Folder 4-6)
      - General, 1966-68 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Campus unrest
        - 1963-69 (Folder 2-3)
        - 1965-1970 (Folder 4)
        - 1967-68 (Folder 5)
        - 1968 (Folder 6)
        - 1969 (Folder 7)
        - 1970 (Folder 8)
    - Santa Barbara, riot, 1970 (Folder 9)
  - "The Web of the Left - Inter-relationships Between Various Left-leaning Organizations Active in the Bay Area," Berkeley, April 1967 (Folder 10)